A Guide to the Alfred E. Cohn papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA132
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Photographs and prints, 3; 5 folders, 2.5" Letter
  - Outline of Chinese temple? (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Statistical tables and graphs (Box 42, Folder 9)
    Subjects include émigrés / displaced German scholars; re Library [New York Academy of Medicine?] journals and expenditures; Medical Index Catalogues.
  - Statue of Fabricius in Aquapendente (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - University of Chicago. Billings Memorial Hospital, Max Epstein clinic; sketch of medical school. Drawings and photo (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous prints of drawings, engravings, etc.
    - Cartoon (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Portraits, history of medicine (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research, 1928, by Cartier (Box 42, Folder 14)
      [See clipping books, 365 Herald Tribune 3/12/28].
    - Hedge, M.L. Dissection (?) (Box 42, Folder 15)
- Notes, 4; 5" letter (Box 43)
  Notes on "Lefax" sheets, from small metal file drawers, in original order and stored in 31-5x7 envelopes. Primarily notes on reading for AEC lectures/articles, alphabetically arranged by author [sub-alphabetical dividers were discarded]; also includes notes re ISS (International Student Service) and Institute for Advanced Study.
  - [Folded sheets with names and addresses, apparently correspondence log ca 1941 re International Student Service (ISS)], circa 1941 (Box 43, Envelope 1)
  - "Own notes" (Box 43, Envelope 2)
    [4 sheets, includes quotation for "Abe Flexner"; F. Galton quotation from W. James; 2 notes re Professor Friedrich v. Müller, Munich].
  - "Arteriosclerosis" (Box 43, Envelope 3)
  - "Digitalis" (Box 43, Envelope 4)
  - [Notes on heart disease literature], circa 1909-1930 (Box 43, Envelope 5-6)
  - "Notes on [William] Harvey" (Box 43, Envelope 7-12)
    Envelopes 7-8: [General] 9: A-D 10: F-L 11: M-D 12: R-Z.
  - [Untitled notes, apparently for talk on blood vessels, with references to work of Dr. Lange] (Box 43, Envelope 13)
  - De Lamar Lecture. "Heart Disease from the Point of View of the Public Health", 1926 November 15 (Box 43, Envelope 14-16)
  - [General] (Box 43, Envelope 14)
  - A-N (Box 43, Envelope 15)
  - O-Z (Box 43, Envelope 16)
  - "Abe Flexner's Institute for Advanced Studies." [16 pp. AEC notes] (Box 43, Envelope 17)
  - "University Faculties" (Box 43, Envelope 18-20)
    [Selected lists of European faculties of medicine and science including partial bibliographies for some individuals].
    Arrangement note
    Arranged in alphabetical order by city.
  - A-G (Box 43, Envelope 18)
  - H-M(Mc) (Box 43, Envelope 19)
  - N-Z (Box 43, Envelope 20)
  - "Heart Muscle. Special Cytology. Cowdry" (Box 43, Envelope 21-23)
  - [General], A-H (Box 43, Envelope 21)
  - I-M (Mc) (Box 43, Envelope 22)
  - N-Z (Box 43, Envelope 23)
  - "Art and Science Museum Lecture" (Box 43, Envelope 24-31)
  - [General], "Bibliography" (Box 43, Envelope 24)
  - A-D (Box 43, Envelope 25)
  - E-Mc (Box 43, Envelope 26)
  - Maritain, J. (Box 43, Envelope 27)
  - M-V (Box 43, Envelope 28)
  - Vollard, A. (Box 43, Envelope 29)
  - W (Box 43, Envelope 30)
  - [AEC assorted notes] (Box 43, Envelope 31)